<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<hicksal>
	
	<title>Alex's Book Site</title>
	<sName sNumber="991 414 949" sProgram="Computer Programmer">Alex Hicks</sName>
	
	<book bookLink="https://www.chapters.indigo.ca/en-ca/books/a-game-of-thrones-a/9780553381689-item.html?ikwid=a+game+of+thrones&amp;ikwsec=Home&amp;ikwidx=0">
		<bookName bookImage="_css/images/GameOfThrones.png">A Game of Thrones</bookName>
		<bookPlot genre="Fantasy">
In the game of thrones, you win or you die.As Warden of the north, Lord Eddard Stark counts it a curse when King 
Robert bestows on him the office of Hand.  His honour weighs him down at court where a true man does what he will, 
not what he must. . . and a dead enemy is a thing of beauty.  The old gods have no power in the south, Stark's 
family is split, and there is treachery at court.  Worse, a vengeance mad boy has grown to maturity in exile in the 
Free Cities beyond the sea.  Heir of the mad Dragon King deposed by Robert, he claims the Iron Throne.
		</bookPlot>
		<authorName>George R. R. Martin</authorName>
		<publisherName>HarperCollins</publisherName>
		<currentPrice>$19.00 CAD</currentPrice>
		<bookReview>
Even for someone who has watched the HBO series, George R.R. Martin’s Game of Thrones is an engaging and enjoyable read! The strength of Martin’s 
writing shines through in these pages. Each chapter is well-crafted. You know exactly how to picture the setting and you feel the desires and discontent of 
each chapter’s (POV) character. Watching how Martin develops characters, with all their flaws, keeps the story going as much or than the ‘game of thrones.’ 
If you’re looking for new information in the book; however, you’re not likely to discover much. Definitely nothing that one could really classify as a surprise. 
In fact, it distracted me (for a while) that the two were so remarkably similar (scenes, dialogue, action all seemed to match). When there was a small 
conflict with the series, I found myself noting the difference. This often had to do with the age of the characters (they are younger in the book) or the 
description of a few of the characters such as Tyrion. In the end, however, I was swept up in this epic story! I liked the pace produced by the shifting 
perspectives. The one drawback to this approach (for me) came at the end. It somehow didn’t feel like I’d finished anything. The last chapter was a good 
one, but because there are so many perspectives and everything is still in motion, (despite the deaths) you don’t feel that anything has really ended. In fact 
this is true; the ending of book 1 is really just the beginning of Martin’s epic. 4.5 stars - J.L. Sutton - Goodreads user
		</bookReview>
	</book>
	
		
	<book bookLink="https://www.chapters.indigo.ca/en-ca/books/elantris-tenth-anniversary-authors-definitive/9780765381026-item.html?ikwid=elantris&amp;ikwsec=Books&amp;ikwidx=0">
		<bookName bookImage="_css/images/Elantris.png">Elantris</bookName>
		<bookPlot genre="Fantasy">
       Elantris was the city of the gods.  What power could have cursed it?
       RAODEN, prince of Arelon, was loved by all, including the princess he'd never met.  Where has he gone?
       HRATHEN, high priest of Fjordell, will convert the people of Arelon or kill them.  How will he decide?
       SARENE, princess of Teod, was a widow before she was ever married.  Who can stand against her?		
		</bookPlot>
		<authorName>Brandon Sanderson</authorName>
		<publisherName>Tor Books</publisherName>
		<currentPrice>$10.99 CAD</currentPrice>
		<bookReview>
I really enjoyed this! Didn't quite sweep me away as much as Mistborn did, but it was still a solid and satisfying read. It was rather slow in the beginning 
and had a good deal of build-up as the world and three main characters were introduced, but once all three story lines were thoroughly intertwined 
things started to get really really good! The mystery about what happened to Elantris was super compelling, and even though I preferred some 
characters to others, I was invested in all of their stories and did really like how everything came together in the end. Overall, this was a solid and 
creative fantasy novel with a slower beginning that pays off in the end! I would still recommend the Mistborn trilogy over this, but if you loved those 
books and want more Sanderson, this one is worth a read! - Kat O'Keeffe - Goodreads user
		</bookReview>
	</book>
	
	<book bookLink="https://www.chapters.indigo.ca/en-ca/books/the-name-of-the-wind/9780756405892-item.html?ikwid=name+of+the+wind&amp;ikwsec=Books&amp;ikwidx=0">
		<bookName bookImage="_css/images/NameOfTheWind.png">The Name of the Wind</bookName>
		<bookPlot genre="Fantasy">
My name is Kvothe. I have stolen princesses back from sleeping barrow kings. I burned down the town of Trebon. 
I have spent the night with Felurian and left with both my sanity and my life. I was expelled from the University 
at a younger age than most people are allowed in. I tread paths by moonlight that others fear to speak of during day. 
I have talked to Gods, loved women, and written songs that make the minstrels weep. You may have heard of me.
		</bookPlot>
		<authorName>Patrick Rothfuss</authorName>
		<publisherName>DAW Books</publisherName>
		<currentPrice>$19.50 CAD</currentPrice>
		<bookReview>
I don't have words adequate enough to express how much I enjoyed this book. Kvothe is now one of my all-time favorite characters. The world Patrick Rothfuss 
has created is so vivid and rich and well-imagined. I ate this book up because it was SO DARN GOOD!!! Seriously, no coherent and structured review here 
because I am just gushing over how fantastic this book is. If you even remotely enjoy fantasy books (and especially if you don't think you like fantasy) go read 
this book now! 5/5 stars and a contender for my favorite read of 2015. - Maxwell - Goodreads user
		</bookReview>
	</book>
	
	<book bookLink="https://www.chapters.indigo.ca/en-ca/books/the-martian-mass-market-mti/9781101905005-item.html?ikwid=the+martian&amp;ikwsec=Books&amp;ikwidx=0">
		<bookName bookImage="_css/images/Martian.png">The Martian</bookName>
		<bookPlot genre="Science Fiction">
Six days ago, astronaut Mark Watney became one of the first people to walk on Mars. Now, he's sure he'll be the 
first person to die there. After a dust storm nearly kills him and forces his crew to evacuate while thinking him dead, 
Mark finds himself stranded and completely alone with no way to even signal Earth that he’s alive—and even if he could 
get word out, his supplies would be gone long before a rescue could arrive. Chances are, though, he won't have time 
to starve to death. The damaged machinery, unforgiving environment, or plain-old "human error" are much more likely 
to kill him first. But Mark isn't ready to give up yet. Drawing on his ingenuity, his engineering skills—and a relentless, 
dogged refusal to quit—he steadfastly confronts one seemingly insurmountable obstacle after the next. Will his 
resourcefulness be enough to overcome the impossible odds against him?		
		</bookPlot>
		<authorName>Andy Weir</authorName>
		<publisherName>Crown Publishing Group</publisherName>
		<currentPrice>$12.99 CAD</currentPrice>
		<bookReview>
This book was fantastic! A thrilling survival story with a hearty dose of humor. The main character Mark was such a smartass and I LOVED IT. The voice 
and the premise hooked me in right away and kept me thoroughly engaged the whole time. My only real issues were that some of the minor characters 
didn't really stand out as much as they could've, and some of the science heavy bits were a little hard to follow and felt info-dumpy at times. But the 
human aspect--the heart of the story--was totally on point, and for the most part I just had a great time reading this!
Overall, this book was exciting and fun and oh man, am I excited for the movie! I would definitely recommend this to anyone who likes survival stories 
or funny thrillers or sci-fi with an emphasis on the sci! - Kat O'Keeffe - Goodreads User
		</bookReview>
	</book>
</hicksal>